[
    {
        "answer": "Chicken Little", 
        "question": "In what film did Abby Mallard appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Mickey Mouse Clubhouse", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "TaleSpin"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Abigail Gabble appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Fantasia 2000", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Bolt"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Return of Jafar", 
        "question": "In what film did Abis Mal appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Aladdin"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin", 
        "question": "In what film did Abu appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Mickey Mouse Clubhouse", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Adella appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "The Jungle Book"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bolt", 
        "question": "In what film did Agent !The Agent appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Trolley Troubles", 
            "The Jungle Book"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lilo & Stitch", 
        "question": "In what film did Agent Wendy Pleakley appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Bone Trouble", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Donald Duck and the Gorilla", 
        "question": "In what film did Ajax the Gorilla appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Tangled", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "The Lion King 1\u00bd", 
            "Pinocchio"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Jungle Book", 
        "question": "In what film did Akela appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "101 Dalmatians: The Series", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Robin Hood"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp", 
        "question": "In what film did Al the Alligator appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Saludos Amigos"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dinosaur", 
        "question": "In what film did Aladar appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            " The Movie", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Little Mermaid"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin", 
        "question": "In what film did Aladdin appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Robin Hood"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Home on the Range", 
        "question": "In what film did Alameda Slim appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Robin Hood", 
        "question": "In what film did Alan-a-Dale appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Alana appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Alcmene appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", 
        "question": "In what film did Alice appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Make Mine Music", 
        "question": "In what film did Alice Bluebonnet appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Wise Little Hen", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Bambi II", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", 
        "question": "In what film did Alice's Sister appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Amelia Gabble appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Jungle Cubs", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Fox and the Hound", 
        "question": "In what film did Amos Slade appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Hercules", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Amphitryon appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Cinderella", 
        "question": "In what film did Anastasia Tremaine appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mulan", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Bolt", 
            "A Goofy Movie", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Brother Bear 2", 
        "question": "In what film did Anda appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "The Fox and the Hound 2"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Andrina appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
        "question": "In what film did Angel appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mulan", 
            "Bone Trouble", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Aladdin"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
        "question": "In what film did Angelique appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bambi", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Mulan 2", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Trolley Troubles"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
        "question": "In what film did Angus MacBadger appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "The Fox and the Hound 2"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "101 Dalmatians", 
        "question": "In what film did Anita Radcliffe appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "A Goofy Movie", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "Silly Symphonies"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Frozen", 
        "question": "In what film did Anna appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Steamboat Willy", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "Sleeping Beauty"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
        "question": "In what film did Annette appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Fox and the Hound 2", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "The Legend of Coyote Rock", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Beauty and the Beast"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "House of Mouse", 
        "question": "In what film did April Duck appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Chicken Little"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Apollo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Bonkers", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Aquata appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pinocchio", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Pinocchio"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Three Caballeros", 
        "question": "In what film did Aracuan Bird appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "Frozen", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
        "question": "In what film did Archdeacon !The Archdeacon appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Private Pluto", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tarzan", 
        "question": "In what film did Archimedes Q. Porter appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Beauty and the Beast"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Sword in the Stone", 
        "question": "In what film did Archimedes appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Ariel appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Lilo & Stitch"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Arista appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "Donald's Cousin Gus", 
            "Cinderella"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Armoire appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Three Little Pigs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Sword in the Stone", 
        "question": "In what film did Arthur/Wart appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hold That Pose", 
            "Orphan's Benefit", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Jungle Cubs", 
        "question": "In what film did Arthur appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Brother Bear 2", 
        "question": "In what film did Atka appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Song of the South", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Oliver & Company"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Atropos appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "Song of the South", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Sword in the Stone"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Attina appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Mickey's Rival", 
            "Disney Fairies"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Home on the Range", 
        "question": "In what film did Audrey the Chicken appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Song of the South", 
            "Lilo & Stitch"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
        "question": "In what film did Audrey Ramirez appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Mulan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp", 
        "question": "In what film did Aunt Sarah appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Brother Bear 2", 
        "question": "In what film did Aunt Siqiniq appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bolt", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Bonkers", 
            "Bambi II", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Brother Bear 2", 
        "question": "In what film did Aunt Taqqiq appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin", 
            "Secret of the Wings", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sleeping Beauty", 
        "question": "In what film did Aurora appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "101 Dalmatians: The Series", 
            "The Lion King"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
        "question": "In what film did Axe appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Jungle Cubs", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Oliver & Company"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Treasure Planet[29]", 
        "question": "In what film did B.E.N. appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Hercules", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Babette appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Plane Crazy", 
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Dinosaur"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Babyface Beagle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Return to Never Land", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mickey Mouse Clubhouse", 
        "question": "In what film did Baby Red Bird appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Cinderella", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
        "question": "In what film did Baby Herman appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "The Little Mermaid"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Backwoods Beagle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Country Bears"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Bacon Beagle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mulan", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Lady and the Tramp"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Baggy Beagle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Fox and the Hound 2", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Jungle Book", 
        "question": "In what film did Bagheera appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bolt", 
            "Private Pluto", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sofia the First", 
        "question": "In what film did Baileywick appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "101 Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Baker appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "The Tortoise and the Hare"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True", 
        "question": "In what film did Baker appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "101 Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Fantasia 2000", 
        "question": "In what film did Ballerina appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bolt", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "The Jungle Book"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Jungle Book", 
        "question": "In what film did Baloo Bear appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Frozen"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bambi", 
        "question": "In what film did Bambi appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bambi", 
        "question": "In what film did Bambi's Mother appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King 1\u00bd", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King", 
        "question": "In what film did Banzai appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Bankjob Beagle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bambi", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Mickey's Steam Roller", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Chicken Little"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Great Mouse Detective", 
        "question": "In what film did Bartholomew appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "A Goofy Movie", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
        "question": "In what film did Bashful appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "The Lion King 1\u00bd", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Bone Trouble"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Great Mouse Detective", 
        "question": "In what film did Basil appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Peter Pan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dinosaur", 
        "question": "In what film did Baylene appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Fox and the Hound 2", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "Treasure Planet[29]", 
            "An Adventure In Color"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
        "question": "In what film did Bear appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mulan", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Bambi II", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Frozen"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Country Bears", 
        "question": "In what film did Beary Barrington appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Bonkers", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Brother Bear"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Beast appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp", 
        "question": "In what film did Beaver appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Private Pluto", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mickey Mouse Clubhouse", 
        "question": "In what film did Bella appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pinocchio", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Bonkers", 
            "The Princess and the Frog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Belle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pocahontas", 
        "question": "In what film did Ben appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "A Goofy Movie"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Fantasia", 
        "question": "In what film did Ben Ali Gator appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Weekenders", 
            "Frozen", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Peter Pan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
        "question": "In what film did Benny the Cab appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Fox and the Hound"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Legend of Coyote Rock", 
        "question": "In what film did Bent-Tail the Coyote appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            " The Movie", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Bolt"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sheep Dog", 
        "question": "In what film did Bent-Tail Junior appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "The Emperor's New School", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Make Mine Music", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Bentina Beakley appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
        "question": "In what film did Beret Girl appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Mulan", 
            "The Little Mermaid"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Berlioz appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "The Jungle Book"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers", 
        "question": "In what film did Bernard appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Secret of the Wings", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Darkwing Duck"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Country Bears", 
        "question": "In what film did Big Al appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Reluctant Dragon", 
            "Frozen", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Sword in the Stone"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Three Little Pigs", 
        "question": "In what film did Big Bad Wolf appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Fox and the Hound", 
        "question": "In what film did Big Mama appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bolt", 
            "Frozen", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Goof Troop"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Bigtime Beagle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Robin Hood"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", 
        "question": "In what film did Bill the Lizard appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Big Hero 6", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Billy Boss appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Peter Pan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Treasure Planet", 
        "question": "In what film did Billy Bones appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Lilo & Stitch"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Bimbette appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid II: Return to the Sea", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Robin Hood"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did Binkie Muddlefoot appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Jungle Cubs", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Binky Beagle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pepper Ann", 
            "Tron: Legacy", 
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Sword in the Stone", 
        "question": "In what film did Black Bart appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bolt", 
        "question": "In what film did Blake appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tinker Bell and the Lost Treasure", 
        "question": "In what film did Blaze appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Grin and Bear It", 
            "Mickey's Steam Roller", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Sleeping Beauty"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pinocchio", 
        "question": "In what film did Blue Fairy appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Goof Troop"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Disney Fairies", 
        "question": "In what film did Bobble appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bolt", 
        "question": "In what film did Bolt appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Hercules", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Bomber Beagle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Bookseller appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Tarzan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Fox and the Hound", 
        "question": "In what film did Boomer appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Hercules", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bonkers", 
        "question": "In what film did Bonkers D. Bobcat appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Home on the Range", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Oliver & Company"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Timon and Pumbaa", 
        "question": "In what film did Boss Beaver appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Bouncer Beagle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Hercules", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Meet the Robinsons", 
        "question": "In what film did Bowler Hat Guy appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King", 
            "The Sleepwalker", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Song of the South", 
        "question": "In what film did Br'er Bear appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Private Pluto", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Sheep Dog", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Pocahontas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Song of the South", 
        "question": "In what film did Br'er Fox appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Lilo & Stitch"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Song of the South", 
        "question": "In what film did Br'er Rabbit appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Mickey Mouse Clubhouse", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Dumbo"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
        "question": "In what film did Bradley Uppercrust III appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mulan", 
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Porker's Court", 
            "The Aristocats"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Cinderella", 
        "question": "In what film did Bruno the Dog appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Sofia the First"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dinosaur", 
        "question": "In what film did Bruton appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Hercules", 
            "The Plow Boy", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Darkwing Duck"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers", 
        "question": "In what film did Brutus and Nero appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Robin Hood"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Home on the Range", 
        "question": "In what film did Buck appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Cinderella"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Chicken Little", 
        "question": "In what film did Buck Cluck appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Reluctant Dragon", 
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Oliver & Company"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Silly Symphonies", 
        "question": "In what film did Bucky Bug appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Three Caballeros", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Enchanted", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Emperor's New Groove", 
        "question": "In what film did Bucky the Squirrel appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mulan 2", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "Cinderella"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Princess and the Frog", 
        "question": "In what film did Buford the Cook appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "Peter Pan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Bugle Beagle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bonkers", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "The Plow Boy", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Little Mermaid"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Burger Beagle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "The Fox and the Hound 2"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
        "question": "In what film did Buster appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bone Trouble", 
        "question": "In what film did Butch the Bulldog appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Bolt"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Jungle Book", 
        "question": "In what film did Buzzie the Vulture appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "101 Dalmatians: The Series", 
        "question": "In what film did Cadpig appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Make Mine Music", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "The Little Mermaid: Ariel's Beginning", 
            "Darkwing Duck"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Calliope appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Jungle Cubs", 
            "The Porker's Court", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
        "question": "In what film did Captain !The Captain appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Orphan's Benefit", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Blustery Day"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Treasure Planet", 
        "question": "In what film did Captain Amelia appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Black Cauldron"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Peter Pan", 
        "question": "In what film did Captain Hook appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Donald's Nephews", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Fantasia 2000"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pocahontas", 
        "question": "In what film did Captain John Smith appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Beauty and the Beast"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
        "question": "In what film did Captain Phoebus appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Meet the Robinsons", 
        "question": "In what film did Carl the Robot appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Carlotta the Maid appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "A Goofy Movie", 
            "Dinosaur"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", 
        "question": "In what film did Carpenter !The Carpenter appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "The Country Bears", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Beauty and the Beast"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dumbo", 
        "question": "In what film did Casey Junior appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "Trolley Troubles", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "The Lion King 1\u00bd"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Fox and the Hound 2", 
        "question": "In what film did Cash appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin and the King of Thieves", 
        "question": "In what film did Cassim appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Tarzan", 
            "Orphan's Benefit", 
            "Frozen", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", 
        "question": "In what film did Caterpillar !The Caterpillar appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Robin Hood", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Home on the Range"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dumbo", 
        "question": "In what film did Catty the Elephant appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bolt", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Enchanted"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Jungle Cubs", 
        "question": "In what film did Cecil the Vulture appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sofia the First", 
        "question": "In what film did Cedric the Sorcerer appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Donald's Nephews", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Bonkers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Emperor's New Groove", 
        "question": "In what film did Chaca appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mulan", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Chicken Little"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Belle's Magical World", 
        "question": "In what film did Chandeleria appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Robin Hood"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers", 
        "question": "In what film did Chair Mouse appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "The Little Mermaid II: Return to the Sea", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Goof Troop"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Goof Troop", 
        "question": "In what film did Chainsaw appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Tarzan", 
            "The Weekenders", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Princess and the Frog", 
        "question": "In what film did Charlotte La Bouff appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Cinderella", 
            "Melody Time", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Robin Hood"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Timon and Pumbaa", 
        "question": "In what film did Cheetata and Cheetato appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "The Little Mermaid"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Chef Bouche appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Chef Louis appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Robin Hood"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Fantasia", 
        "question": "In what film did Chernabog appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Country Bears"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", 
        "question": "In what film did Cheshire Cat appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Tangled"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mulan", 
        "question": "In what film did Chi-Fu appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Enchanted", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Emperor's New Groove", 
        "question": "In what film did Chicha appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "The Three Caballeros", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Chicken Little", 
        "question": "In what film did Chicken Little appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Bambi", 
            "The Lion King"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Fox and the Hound", 
        "question": "In what film did Chief appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bolt", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "The Country Bears", 
            "101 Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pocahontas", 
        "question": "In what film did Chief Powhatan appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Frozen", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mulan", 
        "question": "In what film did Chien-Po appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Private Pluto", 
        "question": "In what film did Chip appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mulan", 
            "The Little Mermaid: Ariel's Beginning", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Melody Time"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Chip Potts appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bambi", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
        "question": "In what film did Christopher Robin appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Cinderella", 
        "question": "In what film did Cinderella appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "Dinosaur"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dumbo", 
        "question": "In what film did Circus Animals appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Robin Hood"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Disney Fairies", 
        "question": "In what film did Clank appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Hold That Pose", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Orphan's Benefit", 
        "question": "In what film did Clara Cluck appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Return of Jafar", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Darkwing Duck"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Plane Crazy", 
        "question": "In what film did Clarabelle Cow appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "The Fox and the Hound 2"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tarzan", 
        "question": "In what film did Clayton appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bonkers", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "A Goofy Movie", 
            "The Porker's Court", 
            "Home on the Range"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pinocchio", 
        "question": "In what film did Cleo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "Enchanted", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "House of Mouse", 
            "Lady and the Tramp"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Clio appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
        "question": "In what film did Clopin Trouillefou appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Clotho appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Lion King 1\u00bd", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sofia the First", 
        "question": "In what film did Clover appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pinocchio", 
        "question": "In what film did Coachman !The Coachman appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Tarzan", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lilo & Stitch", 
        "question": "In what film did Cobra Bubbles appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "The Country Bears", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Tangled"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
        "question": "In what film did Codfish appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bambi", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "Cinderella"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers Down Under", 
        "question": "In what film did Cody appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "House of Mouse", 
            "Tangled", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Cogsworth appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Enchanted", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Sheep Dog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
        "question": "In what film did Colette appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Pooh's Heffalump Movie", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "101 Dalmatians", 
        "question": "In what film did Colonel !The Colonel appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Bonkers", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Chicken Little"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Jungle Book", 
        "question": "In what film did Colonel Hathi appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Frozen", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Home on the Range"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
        "question": "In what film did Commander Lyle Rourke appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "A Goofy Movie", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Darkwing Duck"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
        "question": "In what film did Cookie appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dumbo", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "Dumbo"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Fox and the Hound", 
        "question": "In what film did Copper appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Treasure Planet[29]", 
            "Tarzan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Meet the Robinsons", 
        "question": "In what film did Cornelius Robinson appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Aristocats", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Robin Hood"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Princess and the Frog", 
        "question": "In what film did Cousin Randy appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Belle's Magical World", 
        "question": "In what film did Crane appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "The Aristocats"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Black Cauldron", 
        "question": "In what film did Creeper appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mulan", 
        "question": "In what film did Cri-Kee appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "Fun and Fancy Free", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Peter Pan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Peter Pan", 
        "question": "In what film did Crocodile !The Crocodile (Tick Tock) appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "101 Dalmatians", 
        "question": "In what film did Cruella de Vil [a.k.a. De Vil] appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "The Little Mermaid II: Return to the Sea", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Bolt"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Peter Pan", 
        "question": "In what film did Cubby appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Cinderella", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Blustery Day", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Sofia the First"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
        "question": "In what film did Cyril Proudbottom appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Big Hero 6", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mr. Duck Steps Out", 
        "question": "In what film did Daisy Duck appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pete's Dragon", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Private Pluto", 
        "question": "In what film did Dale appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Frozen", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Black Cauldron", 
        "question": "In what film did Dallben appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Frozen", 
            "Mickey's Rival", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Aladdin in Nasira's Revenge", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
        "question": "In what film did Danielle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Tarzan", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Donald's Nephews", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Return to Never Land", 
        "question": "In what film did Danny appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "My Friends Tigger & Pooh", 
        "question": "In what film did Darby appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Country Bears", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp", 
        "question": "In what film did Darling appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Fantasia 2000", 
            "The Chain Gang", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lilo & Stitch", 
        "question": "In what film did David Kawena appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Wise Little Hen", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "The Black Cauldron"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Demetrius appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Brother Bear", 
        "question": "In what film did Denahi appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Belle's Magical World"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did Derek Blunt appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Wise Little Hen", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Mulan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Oliver & Company", 
        "question": "In what film did DeSoto appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "The Legend of Coyote Rock", 
            "Fun and Fancy Free", 
            "101 Dalmatians: The Series", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Donald's Nephews", 
        "question": "In what film did Dewey appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
            "Dinosaur"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Country Bears", 
        "question": "In what film did Dex Barrington appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Mulan", 
            "The Lion King 1\u00bd", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sleeping Beauty", 
        "question": "In what film did Diablo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Pinocchio"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers", 
        "question": "In what film did Digger the Mole appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Frozen"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Dijon the Thief appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bambi", 
            "Jungle Cubs", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Melody Time"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", 
        "question": "In what film did Dinah the Cat appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dumbo", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Robin Hood"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Sleepwalker", 
        "question": "In what film did Dinah the Dachshund appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Big Hero 6", 
            "The Lion King"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Fox and the Hound", 
        "question": "In what film did Dinky appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Fantasia 2000", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Mickey Mouse Clubhouse"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bolt", 
        "question": "In what film did Director !The Director appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "House of Mouse", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Fox and the Hound 2", 
        "question": "In what film did Dixie appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Jungle Book", 
        "question": "In what film did Dizzie the Vulture appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Frozen", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Pocahontas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
        "question": "In what film did Djali appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
        "question": "In what film did Doc appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Frozen"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers Down Under", 
        "question": "In what film did Doctor Mouse appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "House of Mouse", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Donald's Nephews", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Beauty and the Beast"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Oliver & Company", 
        "question": "In what film did Dodger appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Lion King"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", 
        "question": "In what film did Dodo !The Dodo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "House of Mouse", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
        "question": "In what film did Dog Catcher !The Dog Catcher appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            " The Movie", 
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "TaleSpin"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Black Cauldron", 
        "question": "In what film did Doli appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Secret of the Wings", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Lilo & Stitch"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "TaleSpin", 
        "question": "In what film did Don Karnage appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Country Bears", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Bambi II"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Wise Little Hen", 
        "question": "In what film did Donald Duck appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Doofus Drake appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "Cinderella"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", 
        "question": "In what film did Doorknob !The Doorknob appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Fun and Fancy Free", 
            "Sofia the First"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Cinderella", 
        "question": "In what film did Doorman !The Doorman appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
        "question": "In what film did Dopey appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin and the King of Thieves", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Frozen"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Meet the Robinsons", 
        "question": "In what film did Doris appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Fun and Fancy Free", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", 
        "question": "In what film did Dormouse !The Dormouse appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bolt", 
        "question": "In what film did Dr. Calico appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Song of the South", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Great Mouse Detective", 
        "question": "In what film did Dr. David Q. Dawson appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Cinderella", 
            "Mickey Mouse Clubhouse", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Bambi"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Treasure Planet", 
        "question": "In what film did Dr. Doppler appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Tinker Bell and the Lost Treasure", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Donald's Nephews"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Princess and the Frog", 
        "question": "In what film did Dr. Facilier appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bolt", 
        "question": "In what film did Dr. Forrester appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "The Tortoise and the Hare"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": " The Movie", 
        "question": "In what film did Dr. Jacques von Hamsterviel appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hold That Pose", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Blustery Day"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
        "question": "In what film did Dr. Joshua Sweet appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sheep Dog", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Disney Fairies"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lilo & Stitch", 
        "question": "In what film did Dr. Jumba Jookiba appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Jungle Cubs", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did Dr. Reginald Bushroot appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Dinosaur"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did Drake Mallard (Darkwing Duck) appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Tangled", 
            "Frozen", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Cinderella", 
        "question": "In what film did Drizella Tremaine appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Make Mine Music", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Tinker Bell and the Lost Treasure", 
            "Pete's Dragon"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Duchess appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "TaleSpin", 
            "The Princess and the Frog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
        "question": "In what film did Duchess appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "Robin Hood"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Duckworth appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Dinosaur"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Fantasia 2000", 
        "question": "In what film did Duke appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Return to Never Land"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Frozen", 
        "question": "In what film did Duke of Weselton appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Tron: Legacy", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dumbo", 
        "question": "In what film did Dumbo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Mulan 2", 
            "The Princess and the Frog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Wreck-It Ralph", 
        "question": "In what film did Duncan appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Robin Hood"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King", 
        "question": "In what film did Ed appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Fox and the Hound 2", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Oliver & Company"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Edgar Balthazar the Butler appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Silly Symphonies"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Return to Never Land", 
        "question": "In what film did Edward appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dumbo", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dinosaur", 
        "question": "In what film did Eema appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dumbo", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Mulan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
        "question": "In what film did Eeyore appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Fantasia 2000", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "The Pirate Fairy", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Oliver & Company", 
        "question": "In what film did Einstein appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "A Goofy Movie", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Pinocchio"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did El Capitan appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Sleepwalker", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Chicken Little"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Princess and the Frog", 
        "question": "In what film did Eli \"Big Daddy\" La Bouff appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Enchanted", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True", 
            "Peter Pan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers", 
        "question": "In what film did Ellie Mae appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Porker's Court", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pete's Dragon", 
        "question": "In what film did Elliott appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bonkers", 
            "The Country Bears", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Silly Symphonies", 
        "question": "In what film did Elmer Elephant appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Aristocats", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Tangled", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Mickey Mouse Clubhouse"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Frozen", 
        "question": "In what film did Elsa appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Chicken Little"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mulan", 
        "question": "In what film did Emperor of China appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
        "question": "In what film did Enchantress !The Enchantress appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Song of the South", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
        "question": "In what film did Esmeralda appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Make Mine Music", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Princess and the Frog", 
        "question": "In what film did Eudora appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mulan", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Princess and the Frog", 
        "question": "In what film did Evangaline appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers", 
        "question": "In what film did Evinrude appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bolt", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Oliver & Company"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mulan", 
        "question": "In what film did Fa Li appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mulan", 
        "question": "In what film did Fa Zhou appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Sofia the First"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Oliver & Company", 
        "question": "In what film did Fagin appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Cinderella", 
        "question": "In what film did Fairy Godmother appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Enchanted", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Bambi"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Disney Fairies", 
        "question": "In what film did Fairy Mary appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Donald's Nephews", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Sword in the Stone"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bambi", 
        "question": "In what film did Faline appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Pooh's Heffalump Movie", 
            "Treasure Planet[29]", 
            "Hold That Pose"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bonkers", 
        "question": "In what film did Fall-Apart Rabbit appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers Down Under", 
        "question": "In what film did Faloo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pooh's Heffalump Movie", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Home on the Range"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
        "question": "In what film did Fat Cat appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Fun and Fancy Free", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "Beauty and the Beast"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Jungle Book", 
        "question": "In what film did Father Wolf appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sleeping Beauty", 
        "question": "In what film did Fauna appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
            "Tarzan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Disney Fairies", 
        "question": "In what film did Fawn appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "Dumbo"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Great Mouse Detective", 
        "question": "In what film did Felicia the Cat appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Lion King"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Fenton Crackshell (Gizmoduck) appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Donald's Nephews", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
        "question": "In what film did Fenton Q. Harcourt appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Porker's Court", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "The Country Bears", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mickey's Steam Roller", 
        "question": "In what film did Ferdie Fieldmouse appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Secret of the Wings", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Melody Time"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Silly Symphonies", 
        "question": "In what film did Ferdinand the Bull appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Disney Fairies"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Black Cauldron", 
        "question": "In what film did Fflewddur Fflam appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Pinocchio"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Great Mouse Detective", 
        "question": "In what film did Fidget appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "101 Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Three Little Pigs", 
        "question": "In what film did Fiddler Pig appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bone Trouble", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "Aladdin"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
        "question": "In what film did Fife the Piccolo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "The Chain Gang", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Frozen"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Three Little Pigs", 
        "question": "In what film did Fifer Pig appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Fifi the Featherduster appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "TaleSpin", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Donald's Nephews", 
            "The Fox and the Hound"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pinocchio", 
        "question": "In what film did Figaro the Cat appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Fantasia", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "The Princess and the Frog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Journey into Imagination with Figment", 
        "question": "In what film did Figment appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "The Porker's Court", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Plane Crazy", 
            "Disney Fairies"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mulan", 
        "question": "In what film did First Ancestor Fa appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bolt", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Hercules", 
            "The Country Bears"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Fantasia 2000", 
        "question": "In what film did Firebird !The Firebird appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Robin Hood", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "The Little Mermaid: Ariel's Beginning", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Chicken Little", 
        "question": "In what film did Fish Out of Water appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Tangled", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Wreck-It Ralph", 
        "question": "In what film did Fix-It Felix, Jr. appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Fantasia", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Pocahontas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Jungle Book", 
        "question": "In what film did Flaps the Vulture appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Brother Bear", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Flintheart Glomgold appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Lady and the Tramp"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pocahontas", 
        "question": "In what film did Flit appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dumbo", 
            "Frozen", 
            "The Weekenders", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sleeping Beauty", 
        "question": "In what film did Flora appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Peter Pan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Flotsam and Jetsam appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mulan", 
            "Frozen", 
            "Fantasia 2000", 
            "Tangled", 
            "Peter Pan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Flounder appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Tangled", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Dinosaur"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bambi", 
        "question": "In what film did Flower appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Fantasia 2000", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "The Little Mermaid"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Jungle Book", 
        "question": "In what film did Flunkey the Baboon appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tangled", 
        "question": "In what film did Flynn Rider appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "The Little Mermaid II: Return to the Sea", 
            "Bonkers", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Cinderella", 
        "question": "In what film did Footman appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Brother Bear", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Jungle Cubs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
        "question": "In what film did Forte the Pipe Organ appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Make Mine Music"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Chicken Little", 
        "question": "In what film did Foxy Loxy appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Robin Hood", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Higglytown Heroes", 
        "question": "In what film did Fran appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Hercules", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Oliver & Company", 
        "question": "In what film did Francis appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Goof Troop", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Disney Fairies"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
        "question": "In what film did Francois appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Chicken Little", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Return of Jafar", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers Down Under", 
        "question": "In what film did Francois appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Bolt", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Silly Symphonies"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers Down Under", 
        "question": "In what film did Frank appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Reluctant Dragon", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Song of the South"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Meet the Robinsons", 
        "question": "In what film did Frankie the Frog appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Jungle Cubs", 
            "Enchanted"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Meet the Robinsons", 
        "question": "In what film did Franny Robinson appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "101 Dalmatians: The Series"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Timon and Pumbaa", 
        "question": "In what film did Fred appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Mickey Mouse Clubhouse", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Robin Hood", 
        "question": "In what film did Friar Tuck appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bambi", 
        "question": "In what film did Friend Owl appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Grin and Bear It", 
            "Lady and the Tramp"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Frou-Frou appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
        "question": "In what film did Gadget Hackwrench appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Hercules", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
        "question": "In what film did Gaetan \"Mole\" Moli\u00e9re appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Aristocats", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "The Princess and the Frog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lilo & Stitch", 
        "question": "In what film did Captain Gantu appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hold That Pose", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Three Little Pigs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Gaston appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Donald's Nephews", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Lion King"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Wreck-It Ralph", 
        "question": "In what film did General Hologram appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Donald's Nephews", 
            "Tinker Bell and the Lost Treasure", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Bambi"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mulan", 
        "question": "In what film did General Li appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Country Bears", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin", 
        "question": "In what film did Genie appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Bonkers", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Peter Pan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Peter Pan", 
        "question": "In what film did George Darling appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Treasure Planet[29]", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "Dinosaur"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Georges Hautecourt appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "Secret of the Wings", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "The Three Caballeros", 
            "The Little Mermaid"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Oliver & Company", 
        "question": "In what film did Georgette appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Pinocchio"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pinocchio", 
        "question": "In what film did Geppetto appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dumbo", 
        "question": "In what film did Giddy the Elephant appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Mulan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pinocchio", 
        "question": "In what film did Gideon appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "House of Mouse", 
            "The Aristocats"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Enchanted", 
        "question": "In what film did Giselle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Return to Never Land", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Donald's Nephews", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Robin Hood"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Gladstone Gander appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "101 Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Secret of the Wings", 
        "question": "In what film did Gliss appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bambi", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Lady and the Tramp"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Glittering Goldie appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Lady and the Tramp"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Meet the Robinsons", 
        "question": "In what film did Goob appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Bonkers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mickey's Revue", 
        "question": "In what film did Goofy appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Chicken Little", 
        "question": "In what film did Goosey Loosey appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Jungle Cubs", 
            "Belle's Magical World"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
        "question": "In what film did Gopher appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did Gosalyn Mallard appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Lady and the Tramp"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pocahontas", 
        "question": "In what film did Governor John Ratcliffe appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "The Country Bears", 
            "Bambi", 
            "The Little Mermaid"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Home on the Range", 
        "question": "In what film did Grace appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Belle's Magical World"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers", 
        "question": "In what film did Gramps appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lilo & Stitch", 
        "question": "In what film did Grand Councilwoman appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Grin and Bear It", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Cinderella", 
        "question": "In what film did Grand Duke !The Grand Duke appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "This is Your Life, Donald Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did Grandma Duck appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mulan", 
        "question": "In what film did Grandmother Fa appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pepper Ann", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Secret of the Wings", 
            "Robin Hood"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pocahontas", 
        "question": "In what film did Grandmother Willow appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            " The Movie", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Oliver & Company"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Fox and the Hound 2", 
        "question": "In what film did Granny Rose appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mulan", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "The Lion King 1\u00bd", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Bambi"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
        "question": "In what film did Greasy the Weasel appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bambi", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "The Reluctant Dragon", 
            "Tangled", 
            "My Friends Tigger & Pooh"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bambi", 
        "question": "In what film did Great Prince of the Forest appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Grimsby appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Plane Crazy", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bambi II", 
        "question": "In what film did Groundhog !The Groundhog appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Saludos Amigos"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
        "question": "In what film did Grumpy appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Treasure Planet[29]", 
            "Bolt", 
            "TaleSpin", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Bonkers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Black Cauldron", 
        "question": "In what film did Gurgi appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Cinderella", 
        "question": "In what film did Gus Lollygagger appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Donald's Cousin Gus", 
        "question": "In what film did Gus Goose appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Cinderella", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Lilo & Stitch"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Gyro Gearloose appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "This is Your Life, Donald Duck", 
            "Pepper Ann", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Hades appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Treasure Planet", 
        "question": "In what film did Hands appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Country Bears", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
        "question": "In what film did Happy appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "This is Your Life, Donald Duck", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Bambi"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Harold the Seahorse appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Orphan's Benefit", 
            "The Chain Gang", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin (TV series)", 
        "question": "In what film did Haroud Hazi Bin appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Princess and the Frog", 
        "question": "In what film did Harvey Fenner appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "The Jungle Book"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
        "question": "In what film did Headless Horseman appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Saludos Amigos"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
        "question": "In what film did Helga Sinclair appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Song of the South", 
            "Fantasia 2000", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Black Cauldron", 
        "question": "In what film did Hen Wen appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "Enchanted", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Oliver & Company"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Princess and the Frog", 
        "question": "In what film did Henry Fenner appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Country Bears", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Pinocchio"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Hera appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "A Goofy Movie", 
            "Hercules", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did Herb Muddlefoot appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bambi", 
            "The Little Mermaid: Ariel's Beginning", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "House of Mouse", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Hercules appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mickey Mouse Clubhouse", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Mulan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Hermes appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Plane Crazy"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Great Mouse Detective", 
        "question": "In what film did Hiram Flaversham appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Cinderella", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Plane Crazy", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Hit Cat the English Cat appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Bolt", 
            "The Little Mermaid II: Return to the Sea"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did Honker Muddlefoot appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Fantasia", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "Home on the Range"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tangled", 
        "question": "In what film did Hook Hand appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Return to Never Land", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Brother Bear 2", 
        "question": "In what film did Hoonah appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Fantasia 2000", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "The Three Caballeros", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "The Lion King"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "101 Dalmatians", 
        "question": "In what film did Horace & Jasper Badun appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "The Fox and the Hound 2", 
            "Mickey's Steam Roller", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Sleeping Beauty"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Plow Boy", 
        "question": "In what film did Horace Horsecollar appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "Brother Bear"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Black Cauldron", 
        "question": "In what film did Horned King !The Horned King appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Plane Crazy"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Donald's Nephews", 
        "question": "In what film did Huey appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "A Goofy Movie", 
            "Sofia the First"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
        "question": "In what film did Hugo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Lady and the Tramp"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
        "question": "In what film did Humbert the Huntsman appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Aladdin and the King of Thieves", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "House of Mouse", 
            "The Princess and the Frog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hold That Pose", 
        "question": "In what film did Humphrey the Bear appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Bambi II"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Fantasia", 
        "question": "In what film did Hyacinth Hippo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pinocchio", 
            "TaleSpin", 
            "House of Mouse", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin", 
        "question": "In what film did Iago appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "House of Mouse", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Bambi II"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Princess and the Frog", 
        "question": "In what film did Ian the Alligator appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Blustery Day"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
        "question": "In what film did Ichabod Crane appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Peter Pan", 
        "question": "In what film did Indian Chief !The Indian Chief appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "The Tortoise and the Hare", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "The Country Bears"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Brother Bear 2", 
        "question": "In what film did Innoko appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "The Fox and the Hound 2", 
            "Sofia the First"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Disney Fairies", 
        "question": "In what film did Iridessa appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Blustery Day", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Princess and the Frog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Grin and Bear It", 
        "question": "In what film did J. Audubon Woodlore appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Fox and the Hound 2", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Darkwing Duck"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did J. Gander Hooter appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Oliver & Company"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
        "question": "In what film did J. Thaddeus Toad appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Dumbo"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pinocchio", 
        "question": "In what film did J. Worthington Foulfellow appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "The Legend of Coyote Rock", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Frozen", 
            "Mulan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Fantasia 2000", 
        "question": "In what film did Jack-in-the-Box appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Cinderella", 
        "question": "In what film did Jackson \"Jaq\" Hopscotch appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin", 
        "question": "In what film did Jafar appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Pocahontas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers Down Under", 
        "question": "In what film did Jake appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pepper Ann", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Chicken Little"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Return to Never Land", 
        "question": "In what film did Jane appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tarzan", 
        "question": "In what film did Jane Porter appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Home on the Range", 
        "question": "In what film did Jeb the Goat appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Hercules", 
            "A Goofy Movie", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Frozen"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Oliver & Company", 
        "question": "In what film did Jennifer \"Jenny\" Foxworth appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bambi", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Bolt", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Silly Symphonies", 
        "question": "In what film did Jenny Wren appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
        "question": "In what film did Jessica Rabbit appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bolt", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Aladdin"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dumbo", 
        "question": "In what film did Jim Crow appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Return to Never Land", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Dinosaur"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp", 
        "question": "In what film did Jim Dear appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Aristocats", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Treasure Planet", 
        "question": "In what film did Jim Hawkins appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Dumbo"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pinocchio", 
        "question": "In what film did Jiminy Cricket appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Beauty and the Beast"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Fantasia 2000", 
        "question": "In what film did Jobless Joe appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Tarzan", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Princess and the Frog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp", 
        "question": "In what film did Jock appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Journey into Imagination with Figment"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Silly Symphonies", 
        "question": "In what film did Joe Giraffe appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "Bolt"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Silly Symphonies", 
        "question": "In what film did Joey Hippo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Jungle Cubs", 
            "The Weekenders", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Grin and Bear It"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Peter Pan", 
        "question": "In what film did John Darling appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Hercules", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Treasure Planet", 
        "question": "In what film did John Silver appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Bonkers", 
            "Donald's Nephews"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Melody Time", 
        "question": "In what film did Johnny Appleseed appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Country Bears", 
            "Frozen", 
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Sleeping Beauty"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Saludos Amigos", 
        "question": "In what film did Jos\u00e9 Carioca appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bolt", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "Pooh's Heffalump Movie"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
        "question": "In what film did Judge Claude Frollo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "The Lion King"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
        "question": "In what film did Judge Doom appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Mickey's Steam Roller", 
            "Pocahontas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "House of Mouse", 
        "question": "In what film did June Duck appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dumbo", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Home on the Range"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Jungle Book", 
        "question": "In what film did Junior appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Bolt", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Home on the Range", 
        "question": "In what film did Junior the Buffalo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Fun and Fancy Free", 
            "Hercules", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Jungle Book", 
        "question": "In what film did Kaa appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin", 
            "Big Hero 6", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Donald Duck and the Gorilla", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tarzan", 
        "question": "In what film did Kala appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Pete's Dragon", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Black Cauldron"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
        "question": "In what film did Kanga appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Home on the Range"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Brother Bear 2", 
        "question": "In what film did Kata appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bolt", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Beauty and the Beast"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
        "question": "In what film did Katrina Van Tassel appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Plow Boy", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Darkwing Duck"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pocahontas", 
        "question": "In what film did Kekata the Medicine man appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Melody Time", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Pocahontas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Brother Bear", 
        "question": "In what film did Kenai appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Fun and Fancy Free"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tarzan", 
        "question": "In what film did Kerchak appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
        "question": "In what film did Kiara appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "House of Mouse", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Tangled Ever After", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Cinderella", 
        "question": "In what film did King !The King appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin", 
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Darkwing Duck"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", 
        "question": "In what film did King of Hearts !The King of Hearts appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Cinderella", 
            "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Three Little Pigs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Wreck-It Ralph", 
        "question": "In what film did King Candy/Turbo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Tangled"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Black Cauldron", 
        "question": "In what film did King Eiddileg appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sleeping Beauty", 
        "question": "In what film did King Hubert appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Aristocats", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Tangled", 
            "Bonkers", 
            "Lilo & Stitch"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
        "question": "In what film did King Kashekim Nedakh appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
        "question": "In what film did King Leonidas appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Lilo & Stitch"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Jungle Book", 
        "question": "In what film did King Louie appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True", 
            "Mr. Duck Steps Out", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Robin Hood", 
        "question": "In what film did King Richard appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "TaleSpin", 
            "Tinker Bell and the Lost Treasure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sofia the First", 
        "question": "In what film did King Roland II appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Aladdin in Nasira's Revenge", 
            "Goof Troop"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sleeping Beauty", 
        "question": "In what film did King Stefan appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Lilo & Stitch"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did King Triton appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Frozen", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Chicken Little", 
        "question": "In what film did Kirby appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Bolt", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Bolt"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "TaleSpin", 
        "question": "In what film did Kit Cloudkicker appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Melody Time", 
            "Disney Fairies"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pocahontas", 
        "question": "In what film did Kocoum appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Pepper Ann", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Brother Bear", 
        "question": "In what film did Koda appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
        "question": "In what film did Kovu appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers Down Under", 
        "question": "In what film did Krebbs appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Bone Trouble"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Frozen", 
        "question": "In what film did Kristoff appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "Home on the Range"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dinosaur", 
        "question": "In what film did Kron appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bolt", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Emperor's New Groove", 
        "question": "In what film did Kronk Pepikrankenitz appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Tangled", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Journey into Imagination with Figment"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Emperor's New Groove", 
        "question": "In what film did Kuzco appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Mr. Duck Steps Out", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Enchanted"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Lachesis appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Bolt"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp", 
        "question": "In what film did Lady appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Silly Symphonies"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II", 
        "question": "In what film did Lady DeBurne appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Hercules", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "The Jungle Book"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Robin Hood", 
        "question": "In what film did Lady Kluck appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Great Mouse Detective", 
        "question": "In what film did Lady Mouse appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Cinderella", 
        "question": "In what film did Lady Tremaine appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Bolt", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Lafayette the Basset Hound appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "The Lion King"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pinocchio", 
        "question": "In what film did Lampwick appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Robin Hood"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Home on the Range", 
        "question": "In what film did Larry the Duck appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Oliver & Company"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Launchpad McQuack appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mulan", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Bambi", 
            "The Jungle Book"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
        "question": "In what film did Laverne appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Fantasia 2000"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Princess and the Frog", 
        "question": "In what film did Lawrence the Valet appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "101 Dalmatians: The Series", 
            "Bambi", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "The Little Mermaid"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Le Fou appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Brother Bear 2"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Meet the Robinsons", 
        "question": "In what film did Lefty appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Tangled", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Aladdin"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Belle's Magical World", 
        "question": "In what film did Le Plufme appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Cinderella", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Meet the Robinsons", 
        "question": "In what film did Lewis appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "Brother Bear 2"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mulan", 
        "question": "In what film did Li Shang appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Dinosaur"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Porker's Court", 
        "question": "In what film did Lil Bad Wolf appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lilo & Stitch", 
        "question": "In what film did Lilo Pelekai appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Enchanted", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Dinosaur"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mulan", 
        "question": "In what film did Ling appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "The Tortoise and the Hare", 
            "The Fox and the Hound 2"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did Liquidator !The Liquidator appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Tarzan", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Jungle Book"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Robin Hood", 
        "question": "In what film did Little John appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Beauty and the Beast"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Melody Time", 
        "question": "In what film did Little Toot appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Oliver & Company"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Wreck-It Ralph", 
        "question": "In what film did Mr. Litwak appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dinosaur", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Meet the Robinsons", 
        "question": "In what film did Lizzy appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tinker Bell and the Great Fairy Rescue", 
        "question": "In what film did Lizzy Griffths appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Return to Never Land", 
            "The Wise Little Hen", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Sofia the First"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Donald's Nephews", 
        "question": "In what film did Louie appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Oliver & Company", 
        "question": "In what film did Louie the Hot Dog Man appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Sofia the First"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Princess and the Frog", 
        "question": "In what film did Louis the Alligator appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Bambi II", 
            "Tarzan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Cinderella", 
        "question": "In what film did Lucifer the Cat appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Cinderella"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Meet the Robinsons", 
        "question": "In what film did Lucille Krunklehorn appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "The Chain Gang", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
        "question": "In what film did Lucky appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Bolt", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II", 
            "Return to Never Land"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Home on the Range", 
        "question": "In what film did Lucky Jack appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid II: Return to the Sea", 
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Frozen"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "An Adventure In Color", 
        "question": "In what film did Ludwig Von Drake appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Pirate Fairy", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Darkwing Duck"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers", 
        "question": "In what film did Luke appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Return to Never Land", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Dumbo"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Lumi\u00e8re appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sofia the First", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pooh's Heffalump Movie", 
        "question": "In what film did Lumpy the Heffalump appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Dinosaur"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Fox and the Hound 2", 
        "question": "In what film did Lyle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "The Little Mermaid"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Ma Beagle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King 1\u00bd", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Bonkers", 
            "Lilo & Stitch"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", 
        "question": "In what film did Mad Hatter appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Chicken Little"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Madame Adelaide Bonfamille appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Fantasia 2000", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Belle's Magical World"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers", 
        "question": "In what film did Madame Medusa appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "This is Your Life, Donald Duck"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Sword in the Stone", 
        "question": "In what film did Madam Mim appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Goof Troop", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Tarzan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Fantasia", 
        "question": "In what film did Madame Upanova appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Peter Pan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II", 
        "question": "In what film did Madellaine appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Darkwing Duck"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Home on the Range", 
        "question": "In what film did Maggie appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Disney Fairies"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin", 
        "question": "In what film did Magic Carpet appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
        "question": "In what film did The Magic Mirror appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pinocchio", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Pinocchio"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Magica De Spell appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Frozen", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Tangled", 
            "The Little Mermaid"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Jungle Cubs", 
        "question": "In what film did Mahra the Baboon appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Fantasia 2000", 
            "Tangled", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "The Tortoise and the Hare"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Robin Hood", 
        "question": "In what film did Maid Marian appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Enchanted", 
            "The Fox and the Hound"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Cinderella", 
        "question": "In what film did Major the Horse appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "The Pirate Fairy", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "The Lion King"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sleeping Beauty", 
        "question": "In what film did Maleficent appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Tangled", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Emperor's New School", 
        "question": "In what film did Malina appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Bambi", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "101 Dalmatians: The Series"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Princess and the Frog", 
        "question": "In what film did Mama Odie appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Tinker Bell and the Great Fairy Rescue", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "House of Mouse"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bambi", 
        "question": "In what film did Man the Hunter appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Fantasia 2000", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Sleeping Beauty"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers Down Under", 
        "question": "In what film did Marahute appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Beauty and the Beast"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", 
        "question": "In what film did March Hare appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Private Pluto", 
            "The Princess and the Frog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Marie appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Home on the Range"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Wreck-It Ralph", 
        "question": "In what film did Markowski appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Princess and the Frog", 
        "question": "In what film did Marlon the Alligator appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Hold That Pose", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Goof Troop"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Peter Pan", 
        "question": "In what film did Mary Darling appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mulan", 
        "question": "In what film did The Matchmaker appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Jungle Cubs", 
            "Melody Time", 
            "My Friends Tigger & Pooh"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Maurice appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dumbo", 
            "Hercules", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Black Cauldron"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Goof Troop", 
        "question": "In what film did Max Goof appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Tortoise and the Hare", 
            "Tangled", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Tortoise and the Hare", 
        "question": "In what film did Max Hare appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Chicken Little", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Beauty and the Beast"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Max the Sheepdog appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tangled", 
        "question": "In what film did Maximus appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Bolt", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Jungle Cubs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "House of Mouse", 
        "question": "In what film did May Duck appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin (TV series)", 
        "question": "In what film did Mechanicles appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Peter Pan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pocahontas", 
        "question": "In what film did Meeko appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Tangled", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Goof Troop"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Megabyte Beagle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Sleepwalker", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "Dumbo"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Megara appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King 1\u00bd", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Bolt", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Home on the Range"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did Megavolt appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid II: Return to the Sea", 
        "question": "In what film did Melody appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Fantasia", 
        "question": "In what film did Melinda appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Melpomene appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "A Goofy Movie"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Chicken Little", 
        "question": "In what film did Melvin appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "The Lion King"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bambi II", 
        "question": "In what film did Mena appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Belle's Magical World"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Sword in the Stone", 
        "question": "In what film did Merlin appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "Hold That Pose", 
            "Sofia the First"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Merlock the Magician appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "The Little Mermaid: Ariel's Beginning", 
            "The Plow Boy", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Lady and the Tramp"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sleeping Beauty", 
        "question": "In what film did Merryweather appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Peter Pan", 
        "question": "In what film did Michael Darling appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Goof Troop"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Steamboat Willy", 
        "question": "In what film did Mickey Mouse appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Enchanted"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "House of Mouse", 
        "question": "In what film did Mike the Microphone appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "The Black Cauldron"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Meet the Robinsons", 
        "question": "In what film did Mildred appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Bambi II", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Dumbo"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
        "question": "In what film did Milo Thatch appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "Orphan's Benefit", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Pocahontas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bolt", 
        "question": "In what film did Mindy appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Lady and the Tramp"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Plane Crazy", 
        "question": "In what film did Minnie Mouse appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Robin Hood", 
            "The Plow Boy", 
            "Big Hero 6", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Tarzan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin (TV series)", 
        "question": "In what film did Mirage appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "The Wise Little Hen", 
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "The Little Mermaid"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bonkers", 
        "question": "In what film did Miranda Wright appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "The Lion King"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers", 
        "question": "In what film did Miss Bianca appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Trolley Troubles"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Great Mouse Detective", 
        "question": "In what film did Miss Kitty appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Donald's Nephews", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sofia the First", 
        "question": "In what film did Miss Nettle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bolt", 
        "question": "In what film did Mittens appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "The Pirate Fairy", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
        "question": "In what film did Moley appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Mickey Mouse Clubhouse", 
            "Mulan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Monsieur D'Arque appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Three Caballeros"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pinocchio", 
        "question": "In what film did Monstro appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "101 Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
        "question": "In what film did Monterey Jack appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bambi II", 
            "The Emperor's New School", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Frozen", 
            "101 Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
        "question": "In what film did Mooch appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Mickey's Rival", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "Donald's Nephews"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Chicken Little", 
        "question": "In what film did Morcupine Porcupine appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sofia the First", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Make Mine Music", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid II: Return to the Sea", 
        "question": "In what film did Morgana appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did Morgana McCawber appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Tangled", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Blustery Day", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Treasure Planet", 
        "question": "In what film did Morph appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Mulan", 
            "The Black Cauldron"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mickey's Rival", 
        "question": "In what film did Mortimer Mouse appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "The Jungle Book"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mickey's Steam Roller", 
        "question": "In what film did Morty Fieldmouse appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Private Pluto"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tangled", 
        "question": "In what film did Mother Gothel appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Robin Hood", 
        "question": "In what film did Mother Rabbit appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "A Goofy Movie"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Jungle Book", 
        "question": "In what film did Mowgli appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mickey's Steam Roller", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Jungle Cubs", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin (TV series)", 
        "question": "In what film did Mozenrath appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "The Wise Little Hen"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Treasure Planet", 
        "question": "In what film did Mr. Arrow appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Tarzan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mickey Mouse Clubhouse", 
        "question": "In what film did Mr. Pettibone appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Aladdin"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Peter Pan", 
        "question": "In what film did Mr. Smee appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Donald's Nephews", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "Pocahontas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers", 
        "question": "In what film did Mr. Snoops appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Oliver & Company"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dumbo", 
        "question": "In what film did Mr. Stork appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Mickey Mouse Clubhouse", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Meet the Robinsons", 
        "question": "In what film did Mr. Willerstein appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Reluctant Dragon", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "The Country Bears", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "The Princess and the Frog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Chicken Little", 
        "question": "In what film did Mr. Woolensworth appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "Donald's Cousin Gus", 
            "Three Little Pigs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Home on the Range", 
        "question": "In what film did Mrs. Calloway appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Tangled", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Mrs. Featherby appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dumbo", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lilo & Stitch", 
        "question": "In what film did Mrs. Hasagawa appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bonkers", 
            "Donald's Nephews", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Cinderella"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Great Mouse Detective", 
        "question": "In what film did Mrs. Judson appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin and the King of Thieves", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Jungle Cubs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dumbo", 
        "question": "In what film did Mrs. Jumbo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bonkers", 
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bambi", 
        "question": "In what film did Mrs. Possum appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Mrs. Potts appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Bonkers", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bambi", 
        "question": "In what film did Mrs. Quail appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Goof Troop"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King", 
        "question": "In what film did Mufasa appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Three Caballeros", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "The Princess and the Frog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mulan", 
        "question": "In what film did Mulan appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Cinderella"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tarzan", 
        "question": "In what film did Mungo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Jungle Cubs", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Aladdin"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mulan", 
        "question": "In what film did Mushu appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Disney Fairies"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lilo & Stitch", 
        "question": "In what film did Myrtle Edmonds appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Darkwing Duck"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pocahontas", 
        "question": "In what film did Nakoma appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Song of the South", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "The Country Bears", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Pinocchio"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King", 
        "question": "In what film did Nala appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "The Emperor's New School", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Tangled Ever After", 
            "The Little Mermaid"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Peter Pan", 
        "question": "In what film did Nana appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Enchanted", 
        "question": "In what film did Nancy Tremaine appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lilo & Stitch", 
        "question": "In what film did Nani Pelekai appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
        "question": "In what film did Nanny appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Aladdin and the King of Thieves", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "The Aristocats"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Napoleon the Bloodhound appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Secret of the Wings", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Fox and the Hound"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin in Nasira's Revenge", 
        "question": "In what film did Nasira appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mulan", 
            "Donald's Nephews", 
            "Tangled", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Dumbo"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Enchanted", 
        "question": "In what film did Nathaniel appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Enchanted", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Plane Crazy"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Timon and Pumbaa", 
        "question": "In what film did Natives appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Blustery Day"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Jungle Cubs", 
        "question": "In what film did Ned the Baboon appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bambi", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dinosaur", 
        "question": "In what film did Neera appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Bambi", 
            "A Goofy Movie"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did NegaDuck appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Bambi II", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Cinderella"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Nessus appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Peter Pan", 
        "question": "In what film did Nibs appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Jungle Cubs", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Bolt"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Brother Bear 2", 
        "question": "In what film did Nita appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Jungle Cubs", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Song of the South", 
            "Peter Pan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
        "question": "In what film did Nuka appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers Down Under", 
        "question": "In what film did Nurse Mouse appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Donald's Nephews", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Robin Hood", 
        "question": "In what film did Nutsy the Vulture appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Cinderella"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Frozen", 
        "question": "In what film did Oaken appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pocahontas", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Tron: Legacy", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Return to Never Land", 
        "question": "In what film did The Octopus appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "Darkwing Duck"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Frozen", 
        "question": "In what film did Olaf appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Peter Pan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Oliver & Company", 
        "question": "In what film did Oliver appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            " The Movie"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Great Mouse Detective", 
        "question": "In what film did Olivia Flaversham appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "House of Mouse", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Home on the Range", 
        "question": "In what film did Ollie the Pig appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Plow Boy", 
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "This is Your Life, Donald Duck", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "The Three Caballeros"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Treasure Planet", 
        "question": "In what film did Onus appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Bolt"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Black Cauldron", 
        "question": "In what film did Orddu appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dumbo", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Pocahontas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Black Cauldron", 
        "question": "In what film did Orgoch appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Secret of the Wings", 
            "Robin Hood"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers", 
        "question": "In what film did Orville appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Pocahontas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Black Cauldron", 
        "question": "In what film did Orwen appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Tarzan", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "The Fox and the Hound"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Trolley Troubles", 
        "question": "In what film did Oswald the Lucky Rabbit appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Cinderella", 
            "House of Mouse", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Robin Hood", 
        "question": "In what film did Otto appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
        "question": "In what film did Owl appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King", 
            "Bambi", 
            "House of Mouse", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Dinosaur"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Emperor's New Groove", 
        "question": "In what film did Pacha appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Beauty and the Beast"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Pain and Panic appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Disney Fairies"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Three Caballeros", 
        "question": "In what film did Panchito Pistoles appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Steamboat Willy", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tangled", 
        "question": "In what film did Pascal appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
        "question": "In what film did Patch appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Bambi", 
            "The Pirate Fairy", 
            "Hercules", 
            "The Sword in the Stone"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Home on the Range", 
        "question": "In what film did Pearl Gesner appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp", 
        "question": "In what film did Peg appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Grin and Bear It", 
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Goof Troop", 
        "question": "In what film did Peg Pete appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "101 Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Pegasus appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Beauty and the Beast"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bolt", 
        "question": "In what film did Penny's Mom appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Tinker Bell and the Great Fairy Rescue", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
        "question": "In what film did Penny appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            " The Movie"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers", 
        "question": "In what film did Penny appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bolt", 
        "question": "In what film did Penny appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Dinosaur"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pepper Ann", 
        "question": "In what film did Pepper Ann Pearson appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Tortoise and the Hare"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Peppo the Italian Cat appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "The Fox and the Hound"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers Down Under", 
        "question": "In what film did Percival C. McLeach appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Bambi", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "The Princess and the Frog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pocahontas", 
        "question": "In what film did Percy appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Cinderella", 
            "Bambi II", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Enchanted", 
            "Cinderella"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "101 Dalmatians", 
        "question": "In what film did Perdita appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II", 
            "Enchanted", 
            "Fantasia 2000", 
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Secret of the Wings", 
        "question": "In what film did Periwinkle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Pirate Fairy", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice Solves the Puzzle", 
        "question": "In what film did Pete appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Blustery Day", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "101 Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Goof Troop", 
        "question": "In what film did Pete Junior appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Hercules", 
            "The Little Mermaid: Ariel's Beginning", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Pinocchio"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Peter Pan", 
        "question": "In what film did Peter Pan appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Wise Little Hen", 
        "question": "In what film did Peter Pig appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Return to Never Land", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Beauty and the Beast"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did The Phantom Blot appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Jungle Book"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Philoctetes appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Porker's Court", 
            "Plane Crazy", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Philippe the Horse appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Emperor's New School", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Winnie the Pooh and the Blustery Day", 
        "question": "In what film did Piglet appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Mickey Mouse Clubhouse", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Enchanted", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pinocchio", 
        "question": "In what film did Pinocchio appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Mickey's Steam Roller", 
            "The Little Mermaid II: Return to the Sea", 
            "Return to Never Land"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Enchanted", 
        "question": "In what film did Pip appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pete's Dragon", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Goof Troop", 
        "question": "In what film did Pistol Pete appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Pinocchio"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dinosaur", 
        "question": "In what film did Plio appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Cinderella"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Chain Gang", 
        "question": "In what film did Pluto appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "This is Your Life, Donald Duck", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Mulan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pocahontas", 
        "question": "In what film did Pocahontas appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Fantasia 2000", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Mr. Duck Steps Out", 
            "Mulan 2"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Poe De Spell appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mulan", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True", 
        "question": "In what film did Pom-Pom appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Fox and the Hound 2", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "101 Dalmatians", 
        "question": "In what film did Pongo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Dumbo"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "A Goofy Movie", 
        "question": "In what film did Powerline appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Fantasia", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Three Little Pigs", 
        "question": "In what film did Practical Pig appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "TaleSpin", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Frozen"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
        "question": "In what film did Preston B. Whitmore appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "The Reluctant Dragon", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Home on the Range"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
        "question": "In what film did Prince appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Darkwing Duck"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Cinderella", 
        "question": "In what film did Prince Charming appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mulan", 
            "The Plow Boy", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Cinderella"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Enchanted", 
        "question": "In what film did Prince Edward appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Prince Eric appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Mulan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Frozen", 
        "question": "In what film did Prince Hans appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Mickey's Steam Roller", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sofia the First", 
        "question": "In what film did Prince James appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bambi", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Dumbo"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Robin Hood", 
        "question": "In what film did Prince John appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Princess and the Frog", 
        "question": "In what film did Prince Naveen appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pocahontas", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Hold That Pose"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sleeping Beauty", 
        "question": "In what film did Prince Phillip appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Country Bears", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "House of Mouse", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
        "question": "In what film did Princess appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sofia the First", 
        "question": "In what film did Princess Amber appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid II: Return to the Sea", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Bolt", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Jungle Cubs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Black Cauldron", 
        "question": "In what film did Princess Eilonwy appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin", 
        "question": "In what film did Princess Jasmine appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
        "question": "In what film did Princess Kidagakash appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Fantasia", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Mulan", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "A Goofy Movie", 
        "question": "In what film did Principal Mazur appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Orphan's Benefit", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Plane Crazy", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Enchanted"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dumbo", 
        "question": "In what film did Prissy the Elephant appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Mulan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
        "question": "In what film did Professor Norton Nimnul appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Darkwing Duck"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Great Mouse Detective", 
        "question": "In what film did Professor Ratigan appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Bonkers", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True", 
        "question": "In what film did Prudence appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
        "question": "In what film did Psycho the Weasel appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King", 
        "question": "In what film did Pumbaa appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did Quackerjack appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Fantasia", 
            "The Country Bears", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
        "question": "In what film did Quasimodo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Lilo & Stitch"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tangled Ever After", 
        "question": "In what film did Queen appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid: Ariel's Beginning", 
        "question": "In what film did Queen Athena appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Melody Time"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Disney Fairies", 
        "question": "In what film did Queen Clarion appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Aladdin in Nasira's Revenge", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
        "question": "In what film did Queen Grimhilde appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Jungle Cubs", 
            "Bolt", 
            "The Sleepwalker", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Home on the Range"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sleeping Beauty", 
        "question": "In what film did Queen Leah appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dumbo", 
            "Sheep Dog", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "The Fox and the Hound"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sofia the First", 
        "question": "In what film did Queen Miranda appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Pete's Dragon", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Mulan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Great Mouse Detective", 
        "question": "In what film did Queen Mousetoria appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "TaleSpin", 
            "Brother Bear 2"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Enchanted", 
        "question": "In what film did Queen Narissa appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Big Hero 6", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", 
        "question": "In what film did The Queen of Hearts appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bambi", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Timon and Pumbaa", 
        "question": "In what film did Quint appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pepper Ann", 
            "Tangled", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Bolt", 
            "The Aristocats"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
        "question": "In what film did Rabbit appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Frozen", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Fantasia"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Fantasia 2000", 
        "question": "In what film did Rachel appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sofia the First", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Hercules", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "A Goofy Movie"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King", 
        "question": "In what film did Rafiki appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Donald's Cousin Gus", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "The Aristocats"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin", 
        "question": "In what film did Rajah appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tangled", 
        "question": "In what film did Rapunzel appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Bambi", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Aladdin"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
        "question": "In what film did Ratty appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Chicken Little", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Hercules", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Princess and the Frog", 
        "question": "In what film did Ray the Firefly appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Tangled", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "The Wise Little Hen", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Brother Bear 2"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin", 
        "question": "In what film did Razoul appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dumbo", 
            "Tangled", 
            "The Country Bears", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Robin Hood"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers Down Under", 
        "question": "In what film did Red appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "Steamboat Willy", 
            "Mr. Duck Steps Out"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bolt", 
        "question": "In what film did Rhino appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did Rhoda Dendron appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "The Country Bears", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "TaleSpin"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Home on the Range", 
        "question": "In what film did Rico appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dinosaur", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "The Little Mermaid: Ariel's Beginning", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dumbo", 
        "question": "In what film did The Ringmaster appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Donald's Nephews", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Jungle Book"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Oliver & Company", 
        "question": "In what film did Rita appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Porker's Court", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "A Goofy Movie"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "A Goofy Movie", 
        "question": "In what film did Robert \"Bobby\" Zimmeruski appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Goof Troop"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Robin Hood", 
        "question": "In what film did Robin Hood appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Tinker Bell and the Lost Treasure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
        "question": "In what film did Roger Rabbit appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Tortoise and the Hare", 
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
            "Tangled", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "101 Dalmatians", 
        "question": "In what film did Roger Radcliffe appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Black Cauldron"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
        "question": "In what film did Rolly appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
            "Dinosaur"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bambi II", 
        "question": "In what film did Ronno appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Robin Hood", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "The Wise Little Hen", 
            "Mulan", 
            "The Sword in the Stone"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
        "question": "In what film did Roo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hold That Pose", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Roquefort the Mouse appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "A Goofy Movie", 
            "Fantasia 2000"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Oliver & Company", 
        "question": "In what film did Roscoe appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Pocahontas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", 
        "question": "In what film did The Rose appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "The Princess and the Frog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Disney Fairies", 
        "question": "In what film did Rosetta appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Chicken Little"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "A Goofy Movie", 
        "question": "In what film did Roxanne appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
        "question": "In what film did Ruby appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "A Goofy Movie", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "The Princess and the Frog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers", 
        "question": "In what film did Rufus appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sofia the First", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Fantasia 2000", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Aladdin"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Chicken Little", 
        "question": "In what film did Runt of the Litter appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Fantasia 2000", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Cinderella"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Home on the Range", 
        "question": "In what film did Rusty the Dog appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "House of Mouse"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Brother Bear", 
        "question": "In what film did Rutt and Tuke appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Song of the South"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin and the King of Thieves", 
        "question": "In what film did Sa'luk appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bolt", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin (TV series)", 
        "question": "In what film did Sadira appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Private Pluto", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tron: Legacy", 
        "question": "In what film did Sam Flynn appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Bolt"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Home on the Range", 
        "question": "In what film did Sam the Sheriff appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dumbo", 
            "Tron: Legacy", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "The Princess and the Frog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King", 
        "question": "In what film did Sarabi appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "House of Mouse"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King", 
        "question": "In what film did Sarafina appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "Peter Pan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Treasure Planet", 
        "question": "In what film did Sarah Hawkins appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Bambi", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Aladdin and the King of Thieves"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II", 
        "question": "In what film did Sarousch appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Tarzan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
        "question": "In what film did Scamp appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Silly Symphonies"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King", 
        "question": "In what film did Scar appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Bambi II", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Scat Cat appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Three Little Pigs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
        "question": "In what film did Scratchy appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Donald's Nephews", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Return to Never Land", 
            "Mulan 2", 
            "Lilo & Stitch"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Scrooge McDuck appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Tangled", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Treasure Planet", 
        "question": "In what film did Scroop appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pete's Dragon", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Scuttle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Sebastian appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Chicken Little", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Lilo & Stitch"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
        "question": "In what film did Secretary Bird appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Porker's Court", 
            "Hold That Pose", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Enchanted", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Wreck-It Ralph", 
        "question": "In what film did Sergeant Calhoun appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Song of the South", 
            "A Goofy Movie", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Peter Pan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "101 Dalmatians", 
        "question": "In what film did Sgt. Tibbs appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "My Friends Tigger & Pooh", 
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mulan", 
        "question": "In what film did Shan Yu appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Hercules", 
            "The Jungle Book"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Jungle Book", 
        "question": "In what film did Shanti (The Girl) appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bolt", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "My Friends Tigger & Pooh"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mulan 2", 
        "question": "In what film did Sha-ron appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King", 
        "question": "In what film did Shenzi appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Pocahontas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Jungle Book", 
        "question": "In what film did Shere Khan appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Lady and the Tramp"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Robin Hood", 
        "question": "In what film did Sheriff of Nottingham appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Pocahontas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Shun Gon the Chinese Cat appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Cinderella"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp", 
        "question": "In what film did Si & Am appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Meet the Robinsons"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Disney Fairies", 
        "question": "In what film did Silvermist appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True", 
            "Bolt"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King", 
        "question": "In what film did Simba appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "Mulan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Sword in the Stone", 
        "question": "In what film did Sir Ector appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Wise Little Hen", 
            "Hercules", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Reluctant Dragon", 
        "question": "In what film did Sir Giles appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Bolt", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Home on the Range"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Robin Hood", 
        "question": "In what film did Sir Hiss appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Donald's Cousin Gus", 
            "Cinderella"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Sword in the Stone", 
        "question": "In what film did Sir Kay appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Home on the Range"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Sword in the Stone", 
        "question": "In what film did Sir Pellinore appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mickey Mouse Clubhouse", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Frozen", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Robin Hood", 
        "question": "In what film did Sis Bunny appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Brother Bear", 
        "question": "In what film did Sitka appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Robin Hood", 
        "question": "In what film did Skippy Bunny appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
        "question": "In what film did Sleepy appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Home on the Range", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Little Mermaid"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Peter Pan", 
        "question": "In what film did Slightly appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dumbo", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "The Chain Gang", 
            "Tangled"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
        "question": "In what film did Smarty the Weasel appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Return to Never Land", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "TaleSpin", 
            "101 Dalmatians"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Timon and Pumbaa", 
        "question": "In what film did Smolder the Bear appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Home on the Range", 
            "An Adventure In Color", 
            "Bambi II", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Oliver & Company"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
        "question": "In what film did Sneezy appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Hercules", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
        "question": "In what film did Snow White appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sofia the First", 
        "question": "In what film did Princess Sofia appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Brother Bear", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Bolt"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Wreck-It Ralph", 
        "question": "In what film did Sour Bill appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "Private Pluto", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Tarzan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
        "question": "In what film did Sparky appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Bambi II", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Mickey's Steam Roller"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Timon and Pumbaa", 
        "question": "In what film did Speedy the Snail appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Darkwing Duck"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "101 Dalmatians: The Series", 
        "question": "In what film did Spot appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Sword in the Stone"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Fantasia 2000", 
        "question": "In what film did Spring Sprite appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Song of the South", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Aristocats"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Fox and the Hound", 
        "question": "In what film did Squeaks the Caterpillar appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Country Bears", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tangled", 
        "question": "In what film did Stabbington Brothers appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Higglytown Heroes", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "The Fox and the Hound"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did Steelbeak appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hold That Pose", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Plane Crazy", 
            "Home on the Range"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lilo & Stitch", 
        "question": "In what film did Stitch appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "An Adventure In Color", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Fox and the Hound 2"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pinocchio", 
        "question": "In what film did Stromboli appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Journey into Imagination with Figment", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Tinker Bell and the Lost Treasure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
        "question": "In what film did Stupid the Weasel appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Frozen", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Big Hero 6", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Darkwing Duck"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin", 
        "question": "In what film did The Sultan appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Mulan 2"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Beauty and the Beast", 
        "question": "In what film did Sultan the Footstool appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mulan", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Enchanted", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dinosaur", 
        "question": "In what film did Suri appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Pocahontas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Frozen", 
        "question": "In what film did Sven appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "101 Dalmatians: The Series", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "The Return of Jafar"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Oliver & Company", 
        "question": "In what film did Sykes appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers", 
            "The Fox and the Hound 2", 
            "The Tortoise and the Hare", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "Goof Troop"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
        "question": "In what film did Sylvia Marpole appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Silly Symphonies"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Big Hero 6", 
        "question": "In what film did Tadashi Hamada appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "An Adventure In Color", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Wreck-It Ralph", 
        "question": "In what film did Taffyta Muttonfudge appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King", 
            "Bambi II", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Dumbo"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Robin Hood", 
        "question": "In what film did Tagalong Bunny appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Bambi II"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Brother Bear", 
        "question": "In what film did Tanana appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
        "question": "In what film did Tank appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did Tank Muddlefoot appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Fox and the Hound 2", 
            "Enchanted", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "Lady and the Tramp"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tarzan", 
        "question": "In what film did Tantor appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Tangled", 
            "A Goofy Movie", 
            "Brother Bear"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Black Cauldron", 
        "question": "In what film did Taran appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "The Fox and the Hound"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tarzan", 
        "question": "In what film did Tarzan appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did Taurus Bulba appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Mulan", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Country Bears", 
        "question": "In what film did Ted Betterhead appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Tortoise and the Hare", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Oliver & Company"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Disney Fairies", 
        "question": "In what film did Terence appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Blustery Day", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Tarzan", 
        "question": "In what film did Terk appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Home on the Range", 
            "Sheep Dog", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Terpsichore appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Little Mermaid"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Thalia appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "Beauty and the Beast"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pocahontas", 
        "question": "In what film did Thomas appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dumbo", 
            "A Goofy Movie", 
            "Frozen", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "Pocahontas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Thomas O'Malley appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bambi", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "Sleeping Beauty"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bolt", 
        "question": "In what film did Thug appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bambi", 
        "question": "In what film did Thumper appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "The Lion King"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bambi", 
        "question": "In what film did Thumper's Mother appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Bonkers", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Bambi II", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Princess and the Frog", 
        "question": "In what film did Tiana appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dinosaur", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "A Goofy Movie", 
            "Aladdin in Nasira's Revenge", 
            "Sheep Dog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Peter Pan", 
        "question": "In what film did Tiger Lily appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Tangled", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Plane Crazy", 
            "Aladdin"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Winnie the Pooh and the Blustery Day", 
        "question": "In what film did Tigger appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Cinderella", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Silly Symphonies", 
        "question": "In what film did Tillie Tiger appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "Bambi", 
            "The Little Mermaid"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King", 
        "question": "In what film did Timon appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King 1\u00bd", 
        "question": "In what film did Timon's Mother appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dumbo", 
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Three Little Pigs", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dumbo", 
        "question": "In what film did Timothy Q. Mouse appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Aladdin and the King of Thieves", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Tangled", 
            "Bolt", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Chicken Little", 
        "question": "In what film did Tina appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Peter Pan", 
        "question": "In what film did Tinker Bell appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Black Cauldron"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Weekenders", 
        "question": "In what film did Tino Tonitini appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Cinderella", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "The Fox and the Hound 2"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Meet the Robinsons", 
        "question": "In what film did Tiny appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Frozen", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Princess and the Frog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Emperor's New Groove", 
        "question": "In what film did Tipo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Home on the Range"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Oliver & Company", 
        "question": "In what film did Tito appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "The Country Bears", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Reluctant Dragon", 
        "question": "In what film did Tobias the Reluctant Dragon appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Blustery Day"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Great Mouse Detective", 
        "question": "In what film did Toby the Dog appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Fantasia 2000", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Tortoise and the Hare", 
        "question": "In what film did Toby Tortoise appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Frozen", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Mulan", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "Peter Pan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Robin Hood", 
        "question": "In what film did Toby Turtle appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "House of Mouse", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Cinderella"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Fox and the Hound", 
        "question": "In what film did Tod appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Frozen", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Peter Pan", 
        "question": "In what film did Tootles appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Sleepwalker", 
            "Bone Trouble", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Bambi"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bonkers", 
        "question": "In what film did Toots appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Black Cauldron", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Bolt", 
            "The Great Mouse Detective", 
            "Treasure Planet[29]"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Toulouse appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Jungle Cubs", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Cinderella II: Dreams Come True"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp", 
        "question": "In what film did Tramp appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Goof Troop", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Robin Hood", 
        "question": "In what film did Trigger the Vulture appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "House of Mouse", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Mickey's Rival"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Lady and the Tramp", 
        "question": "In what film did Trusty appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
            "House of Mouse", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "Darkwing Duck"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Brother Bear", 
        "question": "In what film did Tug appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Tangled Ever After"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Chicken Little", 
        "question": "In what film did Turkey Lurkey appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pepper Ann", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "Donald's Nephews", 
            "Enchanted", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did Tuskernini appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid II: Return to the Sea", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "Tangled Ever After", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", 
        "question": "In what film did Tweedledum and Tweedledee appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Enchanted", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Timon and Pumbaa"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Princess and the Frog", 
        "question": "In what film did Two Fingers appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Sleeping Beauty", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Tangled", 
            "The Reluctant Dragon"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Meet the Robinsons", 
        "question": "In what film did Uncle Art appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Return to Never Land", 
            "Dumbo", 
            "Pinocchio", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King 1\u00bd", 
        "question": "In what film did Uncle Max appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Cinderella", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Private Pluto", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Aristocats", 
        "question": "In what film did Uncle Waldo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Tarzan", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Oliver & Company"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dinosaur", 
        "question": "In what film did Url appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Secret of the Wings", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Ursula appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King", 
            "Tangled Ever After", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Wreck-It Ralph", 
        "question": "In what film did Vanellope von Schweetz appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Mr. Duck Steps Out", 
            "The Country Bears", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Lilo & Stitch"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Little Mermaid", 
        "question": "In what film did Vanessa (The Little Mermaid) appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Tangled", 
            "The Pirate Fairy", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Treasure Planet"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Bolt", 
        "question": "In what film did Veteran Cat appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Cinderella", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Sleepwalker", 
            "Lilo & Stitch"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
        "question": "In what film did Victor appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "The Three Caballeros", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Disney Fairies", 
        "question": "In what film did Vidia appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Tangled", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "Aladdin (TV series)", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
        "question": "In what film did Vincenzo \"Vinny\" Santorini appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Hercules", 
            "Belle's Magical World", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Mulan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
        "question": "In what film did Vitani appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "The Country Bears", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Song of the South"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Fox and the Hound", 
        "question": "In what film did Vixey appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "101 Dalmatians", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Robin Hood", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Pinocchio"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Darkwing Duck", 
        "question": "In what film did Vladimir Goudenov Grizzlikof appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Cinderella", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Sword in the Stone", 
            "Wreck-It Ralph"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Timon and Pumbaa", 
        "question": "In what film did Vulture Police appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Lion King", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Goof Troop"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Goof Troop", 
        "question": "In what film did Waffles appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "101 Dalmatians: The Series", 
            "The Little Mermaid II: Return to the Sea"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", 
        "question": "In what film did The Walrus appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Bambi II", 
            "Lady and the Tramp"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "DuckTales", 
        "question": "In what film did Webby Vanderquack appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Aristocats", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Enchanted", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "101 Dalmatians: The Series"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Belle's Magical World", 
        "question": "In what film did Webster appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Peter Pan", 
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Peter Pan", 
        "question": "In what film did Wendy Darling appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "Song of the South", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Jungle Cubs", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Home on the Range", 
        "question": "In what film did Wesley appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "A Goofy Movie", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Tarzan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
        "question": "In what film did Wheezy the Weasel appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Fantasia 2000", 
            "Donald's Cousin Gus", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "Hold That Pose"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Alice in Wonderland", 
        "question": "In what film did White Rabbit appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Fox and the Hound", 
            "The Three Caballeros", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Plane Crazy", 
            "Pocahontas"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Fox and the Hound", 
        "question": "In what film did Widow Tweed appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Cinderella", 
            "Song of the South", 
            "Alice in Wonderland", 
            "Pocahontas", 
            "The Princess and the Frog"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Pocahontas", 
        "question": "In what film did Wiggins appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Peter Pan", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Oliver & Company", 
            "Beauty and the Beast"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Rescuers Down Under", 
        "question": "In what film did Wilbur appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bambi II", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Tarzan", 
            "The Little Mermaid"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Meet the Robinsons", 
        "question": "In what film did Wilbur Robinson appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie", 
            "Lilo & Stitch", 
            "Pepper Ann"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
        "question": "In what film did Wilhelmina Packard appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "Bonkers", 
            "House of Mouse"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Fun and Fancy Free", 
        "question": "In what film did Willie the Giant appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Brother Bear"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Jungle Book", 
        "question": "In what film did Winifred the Elephant appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Enchanted", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "Bolt"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Adventures of Ichabod and Mr. Toad", 
        "question": "In what film did Winkie the Barman appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Lion King", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "The Wise Little Hen", 
            "Lady and the Tramp", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
        "question": "In what film did Winnie the Pooh appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Home on the Range", 
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "Mulan 2"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Oliver & Company", 
        "question": "In what film did Winston appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "Enchanted"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Belle's Magical World", 
        "question": "In what film did Witherspoon appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Sofia the First", 
        "question": "In what film did Wormwood the Raven appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bambi II", 
            "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "Peter Pan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Wreck-It Ralph", 
        "question": "In what film did Wreck-It Ralph appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Sofia the First", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "DuckTales"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Wreck-It Ralph", 
        "question": "In what film did Wynchel appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Pocahontas", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Dinosaur", 
            "Return to Never Land", 
            "Aladdin and the King of Thieves"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Aladdin (TV series)", 
        "question": "In what film did Xerxes appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Big Hero 6", 
            "The Rescuers Down Under", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "The Country Bears", 
            "The Aristocats"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Mulan", 
        "question": "In what film did Yao appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "Brother Bear", 
            "DuckTales", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "The Aristocats"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dinosaur", 
        "question": "In what film did Yar appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Country Bears", 
            "Fantasia 2000", 
            "The Aristocats", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Fantasia", 
        "question": "In what film did Yen Sid appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "The Rescuers", 
            "Brother Bear 2", 
            "One Hundred and One Dalmatians", 
            "The Fox and the Hound"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Fantasia 2000", 
        "question": "In what film did Yo-Yo appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "Aladdin in Nasira's Revenge", 
            "Darkwing Duck", 
            "Disney Fairies", 
            "Bambi"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Emperor's New Groove", 
        "question": "In what film did Yzma appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Wreck-It Ralph", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "Cinderella"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Pirate Fairy", 
        "question": "In what film did Zarina appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Hercules", 
            "Bolt", 
            "Fantasia", 
            "Frozen"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King", 
        "question": "In what film did Zazu appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Emperor's New Groove", 
            "Meet the Robinsons", 
            "Treasure Planet", 
            "Atlantis: The Lost Empire", 
            "Peter Pan"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II", 
        "question": "In what film did Zephyr appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "Chicken Little", 
            "Beauty and the Beast: The Enchanted Christmas", 
            "The Fox and the Hound 2", 
            "Alice in Wonderland"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Hercules", 
        "question": "In what film did Zeus appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Timon and Pumbaa", 
            "Beauty and the Beast", 
            "House of Mouse", 
            "Saludos Amigos", 
            "An Extremely Goofy Movie"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Jungle Book", 
        "question": "In what film did Ziggy the Vulture appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "Bedknobs and Broomsticks", 
            "Who Framed Roger Rabbit", 
            "Return to Never Land", 
            "Mulan", 
            "Aladdin"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Dinosaur", 
        "question": "In what film did Zini appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Princess and the Frog", 
            "Enchanted", 
            "The Little Mermaid", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II", 
            "Hercules"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "Chip 'n Dale Rescue Rangers", 
        "question": "In what film did Zipper appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "DuckTales", 
            "The Hunchback of Notre Dame II", 
            "Winnie the Pooh and the Honey Tree", 
            "Lady and the Tramp II: Scamp's Adventure", 
            "The Rescuers"
        ]
    }, 
    {
        "answer": "The Lion King II: Simba's Pride", 
        "question": "In what film did Zira appear?", 
        "red_herrings": [
            "The Jungle Book", 
            "House of Mouse", 
            "Aladdin", 
            "Silly Symphonies", 
            "The Lion King"
        ]
    }
]
